pknic.net.pk 2006-06-16

# PKNIC SRS - Privacy

|  | 

**Privacy Statement**

|    
---|---  
  
**  
**Nothing is more important to PKNIC than protecting the personal information of visitors to our site. Below you'll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and/or other identifying information) and preserving the integrity of the medium.****

**

##  Contacting the Web Site

**

**If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact[staff@pknic.net.pk](mailto:staff@pknic.net.pk)**

|    
  |    
**** |   
   
**PKNIC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:**

**IP Address**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

**Cookies**  
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your PKNIC transactions. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

**Domain Registration**  
Our site's domain registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their company name, and email address). We may use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

**Links**  
This site contains links to other sites PKNIC is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Payment Order Form**  
Our site may use a payment order form for customers to make on-line payments for our services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to process the payment for the services provided by PKNIC. We may also use the information (such as email) to send information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

**WHOIS Service**  
As an Internet root-server operator for domain name space .PK, PKNIC has an obligation to provide a WHOIS serivce to display the business contact information for any given domain name under its authority. WHOIS service is used by customers to find out if a given domain name is available, or who currently owns it. The information that is displayed is the one that the registrants choose to give out in the PKNIC domain registration form (after they have agreed to display this information). For the public to access the domain name record, they have to know the name of the domain. 

**Advertisements**  
We currently do not display any advertisement on this web site. We may in future use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following option for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications. 

  1. You can send email to [staff@pknic.net.pk](mailto:staff@pknic.net.pk)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. You can modify your own member profile by contacting us at staff@pknic.net.pk
  2. You can modify your domain record by sending the PKNIC registration form to submit@pknic.net.pk 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [staff@pknic.net.pk](mailto:staff@pknic.net.pk)
